{
  "HTMLQuiz" : [
    {
      "question": "What is the command for a header 1?",
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "choices": [
        "header1",
        "h1",
        "head-size-1"
      ],
      "answer": "h1",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is h1. It is a header tag, but the tag h1  is used to add a header 1. "
    },
    {
      "question": "What does HTML stand for?",
      "type": "drop-down",
      "choices": [
        "HyperText Markup Language",
        "Hexidecimal Text Mark Language",
        "Hyper Text Mixup Language"
      ],
      "answer": "HyperText Markup Language",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is Hyper Text Markup Language. It is used on World Wide Web pages to display content on webpages."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which answers below are valid HTML tags?",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "choices": [
        "script",
        "formContent",
        "iframe"
      ],
      "answer": [
        "script",
        "iframe "
      ],
      "feedback": "The correct answer is script  used to add Javascript and iframe  which embedes another doc into your HTML document. The tag used to create a form element is form , not formContent ."
    },
    {
      "question": "You would add the title  element in the body of your page",
      "type": "true-false",
      "choices": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "false",
      "feedback": "The title  would be defined in the head of your HTML."
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the following print out (hint: case-sensitive): p  Hello World /p ",
      "type": "fill",
      "answer": "Hello World",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is : Hello World   |  Your response is case sensitive and your webpage only displays what is in between your tags."
    },
    {
      "question": "Once you deploy your site on the internet, what is the name of the address to access the site?",
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "choices": [
        "WWW",
        "URL",
        "file:/"
      ],
      "answer": "URL",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is URL. WWW or the World Wide Web is used to access your network and file:/ may be the path used to access files on your local machine. URL is the address used to access your site once it is deployed online."
    },
    {
      "question": "What language is used to style your HTML webpage?",
      "type": "drop-down",
      "choices": [
        "CSS",
        "Javascript",
        "JQuery"
      ],
      "answer": "CSS",
      "feedback": "CSS is used to style element on your webpage, where Javascript and JQuery may be added for functionality or responsive design."
    },
    {
      "question": "Whic tag is used to add a photo to HTML?",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "choices": [
        "picture ",
        "img ",
        "image "
      ],
      "answer": [
        "img ",
        "image "
      ],
      "feedback": "The correct answer is img  to add an image into your code. The others, picture  and image  are not valid."
    },
    {
      "question": "You cannot add Javascript into the body of your HTML.",
      "type": "true-false",
      "choices": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "false",
      "feedback": "Javascript can be added internally or externally by using the script /script  tags in both the head and body of your code."
    },
    {
      "question": "Enter the tag used to add a paragraph element (do not use tags)",
      "type": "fill",
      "answer": "p",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is p. It would be called in the HTML as p  Hello World /p "
    },
    {
      "question": "What tag is used to define a table row?",
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "choices": [
        "row ",
        "table_row ",
        "tr "
      ],
      "answer": "tr ",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is tr, which is known as table row, but is the syntax used. "
    },
    {
      "question": "Which CSS attribute is used to change the color of font?",
      "type": "drop-down",
      "choices": [
        "font-color",
        "color",
        "fColor"
      ],
      "answer": "color",
      "feedback": "The attribute to set the color of font is color. Font-color and fColor are not valid."
    },
    {
      "question": "Which attributes are used when adding an external CSS file to HTML?",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "choices": [
        "rel",
        "href",
        "link"
      ],
      "answer": [
        "rel",
        "href"
      ],
      "feedback": "link  is used as the HTML tag, but is not an attribute."
    },
    {
      "question": "br  is used to add a new line",
      "type": "true-false",
      "choices": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "true",
      "feedback": "br  is used to add a new line between elements."
    },
    {
      "question": "How many heading types are there?",
      "type": "fill",
      "answer": "6",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is 6. They are h1 , h2 , h3 , h4 , h5 , h6  "
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of styling does span  add to your HTML?",
      "type": "multiple-choice",
      "choices": [
        "inline",
        "block",
        "external file"
      ],
      "answer": "inline",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is inline, as it does not create an extra space."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the input type of a checkbox?",
      "type": "drop-down",
      "choices": [
        "check",
        "checkbox",
        "squarebox"
      ],
      "answer": "checkbox",
      "feedback": "The correct answer is checkbox type used when declaring a checkbox form."
    },
    {
      "question": "Why add CSS to HTML?",
      "type": "checkbox",
      "choices": [
        "More user engagement",
        "More appealing",
        "Gives the page a unique design"
      ],
      "answer": [
        "More user engagement",
        "More appealing",
        "Gives the page a unique design"
      ],
      "feedback": "The correct answer is all of the above. By adding CSS, more people will come to your site once they have a great user experience."
    },
    {
      "question": "!DOCTYPE html  comes from HTML4.",
      "type": "true-false",
      "choices": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "answer": "false",
      "feedback": "!DOCTYPE html  comes from HTML5."
    },
    {
      "question": "What keyword forces a user to submit a form?",
      "type": "fill",
      "answer": "required",
      "feedback": "The required keyword forces the user to enter a response before submitting."
    }
  ]
}
